# Rogelio Lopez

rogejlopez@gmail.com | (305) 395-2128 | Key West, FL 33040

rogelio-lopez.github.io

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Driven Web Developer with a passion for coding and problem-solving. Thorough comprehension of front-end programming languages to generate custom webpage experiences. Technically proficient with a calm and focused demeanor, bringing forth a positive attitude and a motivation to learn.

## **WORK HISTORY**

Monroe County School District. Key West, FL Substitute Teacher | 01/2021 - Current

- Kept accurate and current attendance records and assignment sheets to maintain file compliance.
- Assisted students of all ability levels develop life-long learning skills and good study habits.
- Collaborated with teaching staff to devise and implement coordinated educational strategies.

Kim's Kuban. Key West, FL Customer Service Representative | 08/2015 - Current

- Processed POS transactions, including cash and credit purchases.
- Restocked and organized merchandise to drive product sales.
- Worked closely with other restaurant employees to deliver great service.

IWPS Services. Miami, FL
Web Developer | 10/2020 - 10/2020

- Responsible for creating entire landing page.
- Wrote lines of code using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript with basic React.
- Worked closely with employer to design a website that looked great and had great performance.

## ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

• Fluent In Spanish and English

#### **SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Node.js
- React
- C++
- Git

#### **EDUCATION**

Florida State University
Tallahassee, FL
07/2020

Bachelor of Arts: Computer Science Minor in Mathematics